priceraja.com 2017-03-01

# Privacy Policy

**PriceRaja.com** is very particular about ensuring your privacy. This Privacy Policy gives you details about our data collection methods and usage. You are advised to please read the Privacy Policy carefully. We want to demonstrate our commitment to protecting our user's privacy. By accessing the services provided by PriceRaja.com you agree to the collection and use of your data by PriceRaja.com in the manner provided in this Privacy Policy. By continued use of the site, you are also agreeing to the Privacy Policy and all the conditions listed therin.

**Information you provide**  
When using our site and services, you may provide information about yourself, such as name, address, phone, mobile, and e-mail. This may occur when you register on PriceRaja.com. Some of this information may be shown or shared to other users by you or by us. 

**Emails, SMS or any other form of communication**  
While you are registered on PriceRaja.com you may receive communication from us in any form like email, sms or other mailing or communication models. 

**Control over the content, service, registrations, accounts, user database, expansion, sharing etc.**   
PriceRaja.com along with their affiliates and associated sites, hold the complete control on the following items, 

  * Registration and user accounts
  * User database
  * Feature and product expansions
  * Data Sharing

**Data Sharing**  
By using the website and/or registering yourself at PriceRaja.com you authorize us & our associate partners to contact you via email or phone call and offer you their services for the product you have opted for, imparting product knowledge, offer promotional offers running on website & offers offered by the associated third parties. And Irrespective of the fact if also you have registered yourself under DND or DNC service, you still authorize us to give you a call from PriceRaja.com & associate partners for the above mentioned purposes. 

**SMS Communication**  
The website PriceRaja.com will send you SMS alerts if you opt for services on our site, even if you are registered on the DNC or DND service, since these are transactional messages important for you in your interaction with the site PriceRaja.com and it's services. If you do not wish to receive SMSs from PriceRaja.com please send an email to address mentioned at the end of this document. 

**What data is collected from you automatically?**  
We will automatically receive and collect certain anonymous information in standard usage logs through our Web server, including computer-identification information obtained from "cookies," sent to your browser from a web server cookie stored on your hard drive an IP address, assigned to the computer which you use the domain server through which you access our service the type of computer you use the type of web browser you use 

**Data which we collect from you while registering**

  * Your Full Name
  * Your Email Address
  * Your mobile phone number and contact details
  * Your Pincode
  * Some demographic information (like your age, gender, occupation, address)

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information about your usage preferences (but not your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here 

While you can terminate your account at any time, your information may remain stored in archive on our servers even after the deletion or the termination of your account. 

**Why we collect the information? We use your personal information to:**

  * to get in touch with you when necessary
  * to provide the services requested by you
  * to preserve social history as governed by existing law or policy

**We use contact information internally to:**

  * direct our efforts for product improvement
  * contact you as a survey respondent
  * send you promotional materials from our contest sponsors or advertisers

The Site contains links to other Web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such Web sites which we do not own, manage or control. 

By giving us the information you are giving us permission: 

  * to provide products or services you've requested
  * to help investigate violations of PriceRaja.com terms of use or to defend against legal claims;
  * to disclose the information under special circumstances such as compliance with applicable local law, court summons, court orders, requests/order from legal authorities or law enforcement agencies requiring such disclosure.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**   
We may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our web pages.

**To correct inaccuracies in the information or if you have issues with the privacy policy you can** Send an e-mail to [contact@priceraja.com](mailto:contact@priceraja.com?subject=contact%20us)
